Now, tell you about several somewhat examples of independent or small team Chrome extensions,
businesses that have been successfully monetized.
So, the first will be gymnasts and I really encourage you to check this page extension
by an article of 8 Chrome extension with impressive revenue by indie developers with Cjmas,
close tools, CSS come.
I will present it as a second one, go full page, spider, night I'd like magic and weather
extension and there is even a blog but nobody knows how they make money and give it
you might actually this extension and has been banned in the new manifest but there are still
some alternatives.
Alright, so you can start from gymnasts, so this is the page.
As you can see, top 8 Chrome extensions that I will show, they usually have landing page,
so it's just a part of marketing, so they work as a software as a service.
gymnasts is a browser extension that lets you sell mass emails in park and banks from Gmail.
A reporter venue was 140,000 miles at one point and it focused on a clear point, use subscription
pricing and it's selected with mostly self-service, so the price you can see, month is 25,
I'm only 18 and it depends on the team, so the team is basically more premium.
Another one is CSS scan, is a developer to extension, letting you know inspect and copy CSS
from animate easily.
Revenue is over 100,000 because one time park is $59,000.
Plus it was 69, 120, but obviously they put it on a page and we'll see it on the product
hand, we'll see even there.
Front page here, you can try it for free and this is how it looks, more than 10,000
and still doing so much revenue.
So this is the way.
I highly encourage you to read about starter story, interesting acrom extension, sexist
stories from pop walls, we see some actually examples, this is the demo that was mentioned
before, Skype virtual as well, we have a browse AI, one up, momentum, rate point, as
other digital product, and there is a code pay and code pay release reader mode, as you
can see, from 0 to eating, it's just article from Jack Wang, and he's extension reader
mode.
So developer launched this read mode, in a weekend, I think got the original video, so key
numbers, as we can see, more than 200,000 users.
And it's premium, we've paid upgrade models, and you can get Ali exposure because product
had actually helped, and if you go to 85, like CSS scan, the premium, we see it was in
future on product hand, so this page probably should try to add, keep the demand there,
always adding so you can stay updated, and maybe copy some of the functionality from other
software, but do not copy into the idea.
Another extension still scan is an extension for front and developers to leave style
upsets with their wind, CSS, reading was around 48,000, but yeah, we have about 100,000,
that was just a start cost, and we can just find it like an identified niche developer
pay point, so stealing website very quickly, it's minimal cost start, it was future
of product hands, so this is like a common thing, as we can see, product hand, starter
story, so starter story is actually nice, because they talk about other businesses, and
another thing is just they have their own page, so not only tells can add the Chrome extension,
even though it has 1000 users, but as a website, and you 1000 users you can get a lot
of money, and last but not least, honey, so this is a big guy, because the browser extension
that automatically finds coupon codes, when shopping online, and it was acquired by paper
for about $4 billion, so it's not in 1000s, but billions, and this is a big company case,
but it's still started as a browser extension, solving a broad user problem, scaled massively,
good to show us what success could look like, and what can we learn from this?
Subscription one type of case, premium upgrades, affiliate commission, like honey use, some
succeeded as well with large customer base, just like honey, but for example, we can
volume proposition matter, so here we had a CSS scan, and we saw real pain, like for example
email campaigns, CSS inspection, so email campaigns for the resource CSS, and we can use
extension as a SAS hybrid, because many extensions, as you can see, they have their own page,
and they can scale it up, because for example, 85 started with the extension, but they have
their own page and their future on started story, so this one of the few extension, I would like
to show you how we can create extension itself, but I highly encourage you to visit started
story, and add the other articles like extension pay, try to maybe follow Chrome extension
on Twitter, to be updated with staff people are building, keep that in mind that you can
add product here to your RSS reader, and be updated with all of the tools, as well I'm using
extension called hacker nether, so if I open it on the right I see product hand tools that
that are getting a viral.